Left-handed knife attack again.
Pisau tangan kiri lagi.
Stop talking.
Jangan bicara lagi.
This medicine
Obat ini
will only temporarily block your blood flow.
hanya bisa menyegel garis keturunanmu untuk sementara.
You should know
Kamu seharusnya tahu,
it won't last long.
tidak akan bertahan lama.
I know.
Aku tahu.
You're a wolf's cub.
Kau serigala.
Don't move.
Jangan bergerak.
If you move,
Bergerak.
you'll die faster.
Mati lebih cepat.
You'd better cooperate with me,
Bagaimana jika kau bekerja sama denganku?
I can help you get revenge.
Aku bisa membalaskan dendammu.
Cricket.
jangkrik.
Guess what lead I found today.
Tebak apa yang kutemukan hari ini.
This time I won't show any mercy.
Kali ini aku tidak akan berbelas kasihan lagi.
The lord requests your presence.
Pemimpin ingin bertemu denganmu.
What if I refuse?
Jika aku bilang tidak?
It concerns Chen Yiqu.
Ini tentang Chen Yi Qu.
Lead the way.
Tunjukkan jalannya.
Wolf Thirteen.
Serigala Tiga Belas.
Save your strength now.
Selanjutnya kamu menghemat tenagamu.
Don't talk.
Jangan bicara lagi.
I'll ask, you answer.
Aku tanya kamu jawab.
If yes,
Ya.
just nod.
Mengangguk.
If no,
Bukan.
just shake your head.
menggelengkan kepala.
Was your attacker
Orang yang menikammu
left-handed with the knife?
menggunakan tangan kiri?
Was it the Inseparable Duo?
Apakah dua pendekar?
Indeed.
Sudah kuduga.
Apart from their code names,
Selain kode,
do you know their real names?
Kau tahu nama mereka?
So they came to assassinate you
Jadi, mereka datang untuk membunuh kalian
because of
karena
internal conflicts among your people?
konflik internal kalian?
Wolf Thirteen,
Serigala Tiga Belas.
are they government agents?
Apakah mereka orang pemerintah?
Hold on,
Bertahanlah.
which government official sent them?
Siapa pemerintah?
Thirteen.
13.
So they are government agents.
Dia dari pemerintah.
Come out.
Keluarlah.
The messenger has arrived unexpectedly.
Utusan datang tiba-tiba.
Does the young prince have new orders?
Apakah Pangeran kecil ada perintah baru?
Have you found the person?
Bisa digali.
Not yet.
Tidak pernah.
This thief
Pencuri ini
is quite cunning.
sangat licik.
No matter,
Tidak apa-apa.
catching the thief can wait for now.
Masalah menangkap pencuri bisa ditunda.
But our lord now commands you to use any means necessary
Namun, Tuan memerintahkanmu untuk menggunakan segala cara
to eliminate that couple posing as spies.
untuk menyingkirkan pasangan mata-mata palsu itu.
But Chen Yiqu has the status of a crown prince,
Namun, Chen Yi Qu adalah Putra Mahkota.
and Princess Li Yue'an is interfering as well.
Ditambah seorang putri, Li Yue An, menghalangi.
With my rank,
Level aku ini
I fear I can't contend with them.
sepertinya sulit untuk dilawan.
Can't it be done?
Tidak bisa?
If I find a way,
Jika memikirkan cara,
it could be managed.
juga bisa dilakukan.
Tell the young prince
Beri tahu Pangeran kecil,
I'll start planning this matter right away.
aku akan segera merencanakan hal ini.
I await your news.
Aku tunggu kabar darimu.
Brother Chen,
Kak Chen.
where are you rushing off to?
Kenapa kau terburu-buru?
Looking for Hou Wei.
Cari Hou Wei.
There are wolf cubs.
Ada serigala.
Wolf cubs?
Serigala.
Did we stir up a wolves' den?
Apakah dia menusuk sarang serigala?
So many wolf cubs.
Begitu banyak serigala?
Brother Chen,
Kak Chen.
where are the wolf cubs?
Di mana serigala itu?
At my family's
Di klinik rumahku.
medical clinic.
Klinik?
Then where are you going?
Kau mau ke mana?
Brother Chen?
Kak Chen.
I'm busy, Xiao Yang.
Sedang sibuk, Yang?
Chief Xing.
Ketua Xing.
Um,
Permisi.
where are the household department files with our records?
Di mana dokumen yang mencatat berkas kita?
Inside,
Di dalam.
on the right,
Sebelah kanan.
the second cabinet.
lemari kedua.
Yang.
Yang.
Has anyone
Belakangan ini,
borrowed any archive documents recently?
siapa lagi yang datang untuk meminjam dokumen?
Chen Yiqu from your department took some today,
Chen Yiqu dari kelasmu meminjamnya hari ini.
said he needed to calculate his promotion date.
Katanya ingin menaikkan gaji dan menghitung hari.
Boss.
Bos.
Yang.
Yang.
Chen said.
Kak Chen bilang
There's a wolf cub at their clinic.
ada serigala di klinik mereka.
Where is he?
Di mana dia?
I don't know.
Tidak tahu.
Someone tossed him a note,
Seseorang melemparkan catatan untuknya.
and then he left.
Lalu dia pergi.
Shouldn't we notify Hou Wei?
Tidak memberi tahu Hou Wei?
Let's go first.
Pergi dulu.
Let's go, Xiao Yang.
Ayo, Yang.
Let's go.
Ayo.
Fan Nan.
Fan Nan.
You lied to me.
Kamu membohongiku.
Do you really think our lord will spare Chen Yiqu?
Kau sungguh mengira Pemimpin akan melepaskan Chen Yiqu?
Don't you dare lay a finger on him.
Jangan berani menyentuhnya.
Codename: Silver Needle.
Kode jarum perak.
At age 10,
Sepuluh tahun.
sold into the secret guard.
dijual ke pengawal rahasia.
At 12,
12 tahun.
failed escape attempt.
[Dia gagal melarikan diri.]
At 15,
15 tahun.
became an elite agent,
menjadi elit.
sent to Yun Kingdom on assassination missions.
Dia dikirim ke Yun untuk melakukan pembunuhan.
At 18,
Usiaku 18 tahun.
became the local secret guard commander.
menjadi komandan pengawal rahasia setempat.
At 21,
21 tahun.
successfully assassinated Helawa,
berhasil membunuh sarang sutra,
retrieved his head,
dan memenggal kepalanya.
earned merit and retired.
dan mundur.
It seems the princess has told you everything.
Sepertinya Putri sudah memberitahumu semuanya.
How long were you planning to keep me in the dark?
Sampai kapan kau akan menyembunyikannya dariku?
Until this life is over,
Hingga selamanya.
until
sampai
death.
Mati.
Enough,
Cukup.
stop with the sentimental talk in front of me.
Jangan mengatakan hal yang menggelikan di depanku.
Is this how Zhao Kuo taught you to handle things?
Apakah Zhao Kuo mengajari kalian melakukan sesuatu seperti ini?
Tell me,
Katakan.
what exactly do you want?
Apa yang sebenarnya kalian inginkan?
If you wanted me dead,
Jika ingin membunuhku,
you could have done it already.
kalian bisa melakukannya dari awal.
Smart.
Pintar.
I just want to know
Aku hanya ingin tahu.
what exactly happened
apa yang terjadi
at the paper mill that day.
apa yang terjadi?
Boss,
Bos.
will just the two of us be enough?
Hanya kita berdua?
Maybe we should bring more people.
Bagaimana kalau bawa lebih banyak orang?
There are so many spies in the city now,
Ada banyak mata-mata di kota.
how do you know there aren't any in the government office?
Bagaimana kau tahu tidak ada di kantor pemerintah?
Close the door.
Tutup pintunya.
He's dead.
Sudah mati.
Shaobing.
Roti bakar.
Want to get promoted and rich?
Apakah ingin naik jabatan dan menjadi kaya?
Get rich.
Kaya.
Of course.
Pikirkan.
How?
Bagaimana mengirimnya?
Let me tell you,
Aku katakan padamu.
I'll be
Nanti,
going back soon.
Aku akan kembali.
Things are exactly as I described.
Seperti yang kukatakan,
You are imperial guards,
Kalian adalah pengawal rahasia.
surely you have ways to verify the truth.
Kalian pasti punya cara untuk membedakan kebenarannya.
You're really not the Inseparable Duo.
Kalian benar-benar bukan pendekar ganda.
Are you stupid?
Apa kau bodoh?
Not only are we not,
Bukan hanya kita.
but neither is Cai Zhisheng.
bahkan Cai Zhisheng juga bukan.
I have
Dalam pelukanku,
a letter from Cai Zhisheng to Cricket.
ada surat dari Cai Zhisheng untuk jangkrik.
You saved his life during the Northern Expedition.
Kau pernah menyelamatkannya saat ekspedisi utara.
When he learned you lost your memory and ended up here,
Dia tahu kau hilang ingatan dan terlantar di sini,
he's been looking for a chance to repay you.
dia selalu ingin mencari kesempatan untuk membalasmu.
ãª
[Aku]
Speaking of which
Omong-omong,
That painting was just something I quickly drew based on your appearance.
aku menggambar lukisan itu secara mendadak sesuai penampilanmu.
And all that evidence we prepared
dan semua bukti yang kita siapkan
was all to prove
semuanya untuk membuktikan
that the Elder Master and his late wife were the Inseparable Heroes.
Tuan dan istrinya adalah pendekar ganda.
If not for this substitution,
Jika bukan karena pengganti ini,
the Elder Master's time
batas pejabat
would have been up in a day or two.
hanya satu dua hari.
He said being able to repay his benefactor before death
Dia bilang dia bisa membalas budi kepada sang penyelamat sebelum dia mati.
would make his death worthwhile.
maka mati dengan layak.
If you two aren't the Inseparable Heroes,
Jika kalian bukan pendekar ganda,
then who killed all my brothers
siapa yang membunuh
last night?
dibunuh oleh siapa?
Last night...
Semalam...
Those who died last night
Yang mati kemarin malam
were all wolves.
adalah serigala.